when it all costs means that you're
gonna play your hearts out to win the
game
and whatever it takes you're gonna try
your hardest to win that game and do
whatever it takes
um that you try and win no matter what
is going on
you always keep your team up you try and
win that game sacrifice yourself just
win basically i do not know what that
means
but i i'm gonna guess that it means
that even if you
have don't win in reality that you still
are a winner and you still work so hard
for everything
um to play good and play fair
trying your best means you have to win
really really really really work hard to
win and to
do well and just for your own personal
benefit and for your team
[Music]
you